New York State Tenants and Neighbors, Inc; Records apap198
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative Files, 1973-2000, Undated; 1; 4.4 cubic ft.
  - Michael McKee Testimony before Westchester County Rent Guidelines Board, 2000 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 15)
  - Michael McKee Letter to Mayor Bloomberg, 2002 July 2 (Box 5 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 16)
- New York State Housing Authorities, 1973-2000, Undated; 2; 4.6 cubic ft.
  The New York State Housing Authorities series is arranged chronologically.
  The New York State Housing Authorities series contains materials relating to the interactions with other New York State organizations relating to Housing within the state. The organizations that are represented in this series are the Rent Guidelines Board, Rent Stabilization Association, and the New York City Department of Housing and Community Renewal, among others. The City of New York and the Conciliatory and Appeals Board files are also represented within this series.
  - Mailings with Housing Finance Agencies in Other States, 1972-1974 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 1)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal (DHCR) Emergency Tenant Protection Act of 1974 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 2)
  - Rent Stabilization Association Brochures, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 3)
  - Conciliation and Appeals Board (CAB) Mailings and Newsclippings, 1977-1979 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 4)
  - DHCR Legislative Proposal, 1979 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 5)
  - Rent Stabilization Association Code, 1979 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 6)
  - The Council of the City of New York, 1979-1980 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 7)
  - Rend Stabilization Issues, 1979-1982 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 8)
  - RSA Lawsuits, 1980-1982 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 9)
  - RSA Lawsuits, 1980-1982 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 10)
  - RSA Lawsuits, 1980-1982 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 11)
  - State Of New York Mortgage Agency, 1980-1984 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 12)
  - RSA Advertisements, 1980-1989 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 13)
  - RSA Advertisements, 1980-1989 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 14)
  - RSA Advertisements, 1980-1989 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 15)
  - RSA Advertisements, 1980-1989 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 16)
  - CAB Budget for Fiscal Year, 1981 May 1-1982 April 30 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 17)
  - Code of the Rent Stabilization Association of New York City, Inc., 1981 June (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 18)
  - DHCR Report: Statistical Summary of Programs, 1982 March 31 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 19)
  - Rent Guidelines Board, Tenant Protection, Notes on Lawsuits, 1982 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 20)
  - DHCR Newsclippings Memos and Speech by Yvonne Scruggs-Leftwich, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 21)
  - NYC CAB Report 1981-1982, 1983 February (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 22)
  - RSA Proposed Code and Correspondence, 1983 October-December (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 23)
  - RSA Proposed Code and Memos, 1983 December 31 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 24)
  - CAB, 1983 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 25)
  - DHCR Memos and Briefs, 1983 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 26)
  - CAB, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 27)
  - CAB Memos and Tenant complaints, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 28)
  - DHCR Correspondence, Minutes and Drafts, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 29)
  - DHCR Memos, Correspondence and Manuals, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 30)
  - DHCR Newsclippings, Memos and Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 31)
  - Cab Mailings to Board Members Concerning Tenant Complaints, 1984 January (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 1)
  - RGB Expenditure Study, 1984 February 14 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 2)
  - RSA Correspondence, 1984 February-March (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 3)
  - DHCR Guide to Rent Regulations, 1984 December (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 4)
  - DHCR Briefs and Sample Forms, 1984 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 5)
  - DHCR News, 1984 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 6)
  - DHCR Newsclippings and Memos, 1984 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 7)
  - Elimination of Rent Stabilization Association, 1984 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 8)
  - Proposals on Rent Stabilization Code, 1984 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 9)
  - Rent Stabilization Association Code, 1984 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 10)
  - Rent Stabilization Association Code Dispute, 1984 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 11)
  - Rent Stabilization Association Correspondence and Fact Sheets, 1984 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 12)
  - Rent Stabilization Code, 1984 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 13)
  - Rent Registration/ Tenant Complaint Forms, 1984 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 14)
  - RSA and Assembly Analysis/ Correspondence regarding Rent Stabilization Code, 1984 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 15)
  - DHCR Bulletins, 1984-1994 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 16)
  - DHCR Bulletins and Reports, 1985 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 17)
  - DHCR Report to Legislature on Office of Rent Administration, 1985 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 18)
  - Lawsuits against RGB, 1985 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 19)
  - Rent Stabilization Code Comments by DHCR, 1986 January 7 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 20)
  - DHCR Press Releases, Renewal Forms and Opinion Pieces, 1986 March-July (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 21)
  - The Council of the City of New York Int. No. 646, 1986 July 10 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 22)
  - DHCR "The Uses and Limits of Rent Regulation, 1986 December 12 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 23)
  - DHCR William Rowen Correspondence, 1986 December (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 24)
  - DHCR Assorted Fact Sheets, 1986 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 25)
  - DHCR Proposed Rent Stabilization Code, 1986 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 26)
  - DHCR's Rent Stabilization Code, 1986 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 27)
  - DHCR's Rent Stabilization Code, 1986 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 28)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal Proposed Rent Stabilization Code, 1986 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 29)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal Public Notices, 1986 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 30)
  - Law Suit: NYSTNC against William Eimicke, Commisioner DHCR, 1986 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 31)
  - Rent Stabilization Code Comments by DHCR, 1986 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 32)
  - Rent Stabilization Code Comments by DHCR, 1986 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 33)
  - DHCR Updates on Rent Stabilization, 1986-1987 (Box 2 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 34)
  - News Articles and Testimonies from State Hearing on Performance of DHCR, 1987 March (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 1)
  - NYSTNC Submissions to Rent Guidelines Board, 1987 May-June (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 2)
  - DHCR Forms and Applications, 1987 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 3)
  - DHCR Requests for Proposal for Administrative Services and Mailings, 1987 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 4)
  - Rent Guidelines Board Submissions, 1987 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 5)
  - RGB Price Index, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 6)
  - DHCR Advisory Opinion Listings, 1987-1992 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 7)
  - DHCR Owner's Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes, 1988 January 15 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 8)
  - DHCR Meeting Minutes with Manuals, 1988 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 9)
  - DHCR Policy Recommendations, 1988 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 10)
  - DHCR Tenants Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 11)
  - NYS Housing Finance Agency Publications, 1988 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 12)
  - RSA Correspondence, 1988 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 13)
  - DHCR Funding and Policy Recommendations, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 14)
  - DHCR Rent Terms Glossary and Applications, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 15)
  - RSA Advertisements, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 16)
  - DHCR Press Briefing Information Packet, 1989 January 19 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 17)
  - Rent Guidelines Board Testimony of Anthony J. Blackburn, 1989 February 28 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 18)
  - NYC Board of Estimate Mailing and Newsclippings, 1989 March 20 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 19)
  - DHCR Tenants Advisory Committee Agenda and Memos, 1989 May 11 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 20)
  - DHCR Review of the Major Capital Improvement Plan, 1989 June 1 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 21)
  - DHCR Mailings and Policy Drafts, 1989 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 22)
  - DHCR Memos and Mailings, 1989 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 23)
  - DHCR Tenants Advisory Committee Meeting Agendas, 1989 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 24)
  - NYC Campaign Finance Board, 1989 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 25)
  - DHCR Office of Rent Administration Policy Statement Listings, 1989-1993 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 26)
  - Appartment Price Indexes for Rent Stabilization Association, 1990 May 3 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 27)
  - DHCR NYC Rent Stabilization Code, 1990 September (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 28)
  - DHCR Agendas and Policy Statements, 1990 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 29)
  - DHCR Agendas, Policy Drafts and Memos, 1990 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 30)
  - DHCR Tenants Advisory Committee Agendas and Draft Manuals, 1990 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 31)
  - NYSTNC Correspondence and Statements on RGB Price Index, 1990 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 32)
  - Price Index Correspondence with ANHD, 1990 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 33)
  - Rent Guidelines Board Eric Weinstock Testimony, 1990 (Box 3 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 34)
  - RGB Price Indexes and Resumes, 1990 (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 1)
  - RSA Correspondence, 1990 (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 2)
  - DHCR Bulletins and Memos, 1990 September-1991 September (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 3)
  - RSA Advertisements, 1990-1992 (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 4)
  - RSA Advertisements, 1990-1992 (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 5)
  - DHCR Program Bill 91-13A, 1991 January 24 (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 6)
  - DHCR Bulletins on Rent Dispute, 1991 (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 7)
  - DHCR Meeting Minutes and Policy Drafts, 1991 (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 8)
  - DHCR Tenant Advisory Committee Policy Drafts and Mailings, 1991 (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 9)
  - DHCR Tenant Advisory Committee Meetings, 1991 (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 10)
  - DHCR Tenant Advisory Committee Memos and Mailings, 1991 (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 11)
  - DHCR Tenant Protection Drafts and Mailings, 1991 (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 12)
  - RGB Submission to Rent Guidelines Association, 1991 (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 13)
  - DHCR Agendas, Bulletins and Memos, 1992 (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 14)
  - DHCR Fact Sheet Spanish Version, 1992 (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 15)
  - DHCR Memos and Mailings, 1992 (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 16)
  - DHCR Policy Drafts, 1992 (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 17)
  - DHCR Tenant Advisory Committee Agenda and Policy Drafts, 1992 (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 18)
  - NYSTNC 1992 Rent Guidelines Board Testimony (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 19)
  - RGB Mail from Rent Stabilization Association, 1992 (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 20)
  - RGB Mail from Rent Stabilization Association, 1992 (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 21)
  - RGB Reports and Studies, 1992 (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 22)
  - RGB White Papers, 1992 (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 23)
  - DHCR Report to the Legislature, 1993 December (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 24)
  - DHCR Publications, Memos and Juarez v. Wavecrest Management Lawsuit, 1993-1995 (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 25)
  - New York City Department of Housing Preservation and Development, 1994 February 10 (Box 4 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 26)
  - DHCR Tenant Advisory Committee Meeting, 1994 April 7 (Box 5 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 1)
  - DHCR Tenant Advisory Committee Meeting, 1994 June 2 (Box 5 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 2)
  - Stabilized Rent is Biased, Threat to Adequate Housing in NYC, 1994 June (Box 5 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 3)
  - DHCR Tenant Advisory Committee Agendas and Drafts, 1994 June-November (Box 5 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 4)
  - Council of the City of New York Memos and Policy, 1994 (Box 5 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 5)
  - DHCR Tenant Advisory Committee Bulletins and Mailings, 1994 (Box 5 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 6)
  - DHCR Tenant Advisory Committee Agenda, 1995 May 25 (Box 5 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 7)
  - DHCR Tenant Advisory Committee Membership, 1995 (Box 5 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 8)
  - RGB Correspondence, 1995 (Box 5 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 9)
  - Correspondence With Mayor Giuliani, 1996 (Box 6 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 1)
  - RGB Propaganda Concerning Mayor Giuliani, 1996 (Box 6 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 2)
  - RGB Propaganda Concerning Mayor Giuliani, 1996 (Box 6 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 3)
  - Rent Guidelines Board Index of Operating Costs, 1997 (Box 6 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 4)
  - Rent Guidelines Board Tenant Advocates Group, 1998 (Box 6 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 5)
  - RGB Reports and Correspondence Concerning Lawsuit, 1998 (Box 6 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 6)
  - The Rent Guidelines Board 1999 Mortgage Survey (Box 6 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 7)
  - Rent Guidelines Board Appartment Orders and Comparisons, 2000 (Box 6 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 8)
  - DHCR Guide to Housing Programs, Undated (Box 6 (2-New York State Housing Authorities), Folder 9)
- Legislative, 1973-2000, Undated; 3; 9.8 cubic ft.
  The Legislative series is arranged chronolgically.
  The legislative series includes bill jackets, legislative memorandums, State Assembly and Senate vote records, correspondence regarding the legislation. The Tenants & Neighbors' legislative committee's related materials such as agendas, minutes, memoranda are represented in this series. Mitchell-Lama council legislation can be found in the legislative series.
  - Legislation, 1974-1976 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 1)
  - Legislative Memorandums, 1974-1976 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 2)
  - Assemblywoman Marie Runyon, 1974-1976 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 3)
  - Legislative Memorandums and Rent and Eviction Regulation, 1975 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 4)
  - Legislative Memorandums, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 5)
  - S. 7287, A. 9257, Legislative Memorandums In Opposition, 1976 February 17 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 6)
  - Drafts of Rent Regulation Bills, 1976-1979 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 7)
  - J-51 Tax Abatement, City Council Bills, 1976-1984 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 8)
  - J-51 and New York City Department of Housing Preservation and Development, 1977-1982 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 9)
  - J-51 State Authorization Section 489, Real Property Tax Law, 1977 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 10)
  - Mortgage Foreclosure Legislation, 1977-1982 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 11)
  - J-51, 1977-1983 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 12)
  - Legislation and Related Materials, 1977 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 13)
  - Rent Control Issues, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 14)
  - Lobby Registration, 1977-1981 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 15-17)
  - Co-Op Conversion, 1978 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 18)
  - Rent Control Bill, 1978 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 19)
  - Mitchell-Lama Council, 1978-1984 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 20)
  - Bill Jackets and Memorandums, 1979 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 21)
  - Co-Op, 1979-1982 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 22-24)
  - J-51 Background Research, 1979-1983 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 25)
  - Statewide Rent Control, 1980 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 26)
  - Legislation, 1980 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 27)
  - ETPA/ Co-Op and Related Publications, 1980-1981 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 28)
  - Proposed Statewide Rent and Eviction Control Bill, 1980-1981 (Box 1 (3-Legislative), Folder 29)
  - J-51 Background Research, 1990-1983 (Box 2 (3-Legislative), Folder 1)
  - S. 1991 Landlords and "Personal Use", 1980-1983 (Box 2 (3-Legislative), Folder 2)
  - Legislation and Related Materials, 1981 (Box 2 (3-Legislative), Folder 3-4)
  - Metropolitan Transportation Authority Property Transfer and Mortgage Recording Taxes, 1981 (Box 2 (3-Legislative), Folder 5)
  - Metropolitan Transportation Authority Tax and Appropriation Package, 1981 (Box 2 (3-Legislative), Folder 6)
  - Capital Gains Tax, 1981 (Box 2 (3-Legislative), Folder 7)
  - Co-Op and Related Newsclippings, 1981 (Box 2 (3-Legislative), Folder 8)
  - Legislation, 1981-1982 (Box 2 (3-Legislative), Folder 9)
  - Intro 1192 Wallace Bill, 1982 (Box 2 (3-Legislative), Folder 10)
  - Co-Op Conversion Legislation, 1982 (Box 2 (3-Legislative), Folder 11)
  - Legislation, 1982 (Box 2 (3-Legislative), Folder 12)
  - Security Deposit Capital Pool, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (3-Legislative), Folder 13)
  - Intro 1192 Including Legislative Memorandums, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (3-Legislative), Folder 14)
  - Waterfront Development Bill, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (3-Legislative), Folder 15)
  - A. 2889 Apartment Hotels, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (3-Legislative), Folder 16)
  - J-51 Mitchell-Lama Housing, 1982-1987 (Box 2 (3-Legislative), Folder 17)
  - Co-Op Conversions Newspaper and Press Clippings, 1982-1987; Undated (Box 2 (3-Legislative), Folder 18)
  - Legislative Memorandums, 1983 (Box 2 (3-Legislative), Folder 19)
  - Co-Op Conversions, 1983 (Box 2 (3-Legislative), Folder 20)
  - CO-Op Conversions Attorney General Regulations, 1983 (Box 2 (3-Legislative), Folder 21)
  - Omnibus Housing Act, 1983 (Box 2 (3-Legislative), Folder 22-23)
  - Omnibus Housing Act, 1983 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 1-2)
  - Omnibus Housing Act Laws of 1983 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 3)
  - Omnibus Housing Act New Tenant Protection Law, 1983 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 4)
  - Omnibus Housing Act Materials on C.A.P., 1983 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 5)
  - Non-Profit Landlords COTONPIL Bill, 1983 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 6)
  - Post J-51, 1983 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 7)
  - S. 2029-B, A. 2553-B Pet Bill, 1983 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 8)
  - S. 1991 Restoration of NYC Rent Stabilization Code for Eviction, 1983 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 9)
  - Emergency Tenant Protection Act Renewal, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 10)
  - Emergency Tenant Protection Act Bill Drafting Commission, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 11)
  - Small Business Task Force Commercial Rent Regulation, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 12)
  - Extension to Upstate New York of Emergency Tenant Protection Act, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 13)
  - A. 50 Protection for Tentants in Garden Type Maisonette Apartments in NYC, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 14)
  - Omnibus Banking Bills, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 15)
  - Legislative Plans and Related Materials, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 16)
  - Rules of the Senate, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 17)
  - J-51 Major Capital Improvements, 1983-1985 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 18)
  - Mobile Homes Bill Jackets and Memorandums, 1983-1985 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 19)
  - Banking Laws, 1983-1985 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 20)
  - J-51 Legislative Memorandums and Draft Bills, 1983-1987 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 21)
  - Small Building Assessment, 1984 January (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 22)
  - Senate Chapter 403, 1984 February 7 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 23)
  - Tenant Alert from Assemblyman Pete Grannis, 1984 April (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 24)
  - Legislation and Related Materials, 1984 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 25-26)
  - Major Capital Improvements Legislation and Lawsuit, 1984 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 27)
  - Legislative Campaign Emergency Tenant Protection Act, 1984 (Box 3 (3-Legislative), Folder 28)
  - Omnibus Affordable Housing Act, 1984 (Box 4 (3-Legislative), Folder 1)
  - Legislation, 1984 (Box 4 (3-Legislative), Folder 2)
  - Legislative Memorandums Including James Garst Statements and Correspondence, 1984 (Box 4 (3-Legislative), Folder 3-4)
  - Legislative Memorandums, 1984 (Box 4 (3-Legislative), Folder 5)
  - Single Room Occupancy (SRO) and J-51, 1984 (Box 4 (3-Legislative), Folder 6)
  - Price Index Campaign, 1984 (Box 4 (3-Legislative), Folder 7)
  - Housing Trust Fund, 1984-1985 (Box 4 (3-Legislative), Folder 8)
  - Protection of Senior Citizens in Evictions, 1984-1985 (Box 4 (3-Legislative), Folder 9)
  - Legislative Memorandums, 1984-1985 (Box 4 (3-Legislative), Folder 10-11)
  - Single Room Occupancy Moratorium, 1984-1985 (Box 4 (3-Legislative), Folder 12)